const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 55-year-old male, diagnosed with stage four pancreatic cancer, presents to the clinic with abdominal pain and jaundice for the past 1 week. On examination, he is severely emaciated and jaundiced. Laboratory evaluation reveals total bilirubin is 10.3 mg/dL, direct bilirubin is 9.3 mg/dL, indirect bilirubin is 1.0 mg/dL, and alkaline phosphatase is 514 mg/dL. What is the management of choice for this patient?","answers":[{"option":"Palliative gastrojejunostomy","bool":false},{"option":"Whipple's procedure","bool":false},{"option":"Endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP) with stenting","bool":true},{"option":"Percutaneous biliary drainage","bool":false},{"option":"Distal pancreatectomy","bool":false},{"option":"FOLFIRINOX chemotherapy regimen","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the range for food items with a medium glycemic index, such as oranges, or honey?","answers":[{"option":"40-54","bool":false},{"option":"85-99","bool":false},{"option":"26-39","bool":false},{"option":"56-69","bool":true},{"option":"70-84","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is incorrect regarding abetalipoproteinemia?","answers":[{"option":"Autosomal dominant mode of inheritence","bool":true},{"option":"Acanthocytosis is a hallmark feature","bool":false},{"option":"Occurs in both genders equally","bool":false},{"option":"Low serum cholesterol and low-density lipoproteins","bool":false},{"option":"Dietary restriction of long-chain fatty acids improves symptoms","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 55-year-old male is brought to the emergency room from his office with a history of vomiting approximately two cups of blood. On examination, he has a grossly distended abdomen with positive fluid thrill. Mild jaundice is also observed. What is the likely complication in this patient?","answers":[{"option":"Ruptured esophageal varices","bool":true},{"option":"Platelet dysfunction","bool":false},{"option":"Vitamin K deficiency","bool":false},{"option":"Hypoalbuminemia","bool":false},{"option":"Portal hypertension","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What laboratory parameter is used to differentiate between biliary colic and acute cholecystitis?","answers":[{"option":"Indirect hyperbilirubinemia","bool":false},{"option":"Elevated serum amylase levels","bool":false},{"option":"Mixed hyperbilirubinemia","bool":false},{"option":"Leukocytosis","bool":true},{"option":"Shift to right","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is the etiology of Cushing's ulcers?","answers":[{"option":"Chronic liver disease","bool":false},{"option":"Helicobacter pylori infection","bool":false},{"option":"Corrosive ingestion","bool":false},{"option":"Raised intracranial pressure","bool":true},{"option":"Burn injury","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 45-year-old female presents to the clinic with complaints of bloody diarrhea for the past 2 weeks. What is the least important diagnostic investigation in such cases?","answers":[{"option":"Sigmoidoscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Colonoscopy and biopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Esophagogastroduodenoscopy","bool":true},{"option":"Complete blood count","bool":false},{"option":"Stool detailed report (DR)","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the below-enlisted food items may precipitate the clinical features in celiac disease?","answers":[{"option":"Rice","bool":false},{"option":"Butter","bool":false},{"option":"Barley","bool":true},{"option":"Fish","bool":false},{"option":"Potato","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 60-year-old man is called for a follow-up 2 weeks after his surgery for colon cancer. During the surgery, his tumor was removed and a permanent stoma was made. What is the most likely procedure performed?","answers":[{"option":"Low anterior resection","bool":false},{"option":"Whipple's procedure","bool":false},{"option":"Peustow's procedure","bool":false},{"option":"Billroth I procedure","bool":false},{"option":"Abdominoperineal resection","bool":true}]},{"id":9,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which gene mutation is most commonly associated with gastrinomas?","answers":[{"option":"MEN1","bool":true},{"option":"p16/CDKN2A","bool":false},{"option":"RB","bool":false},{"option":"NF2","bool":false},{"option":"TP53","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which amongst the below enlisted is not included in the Ranson criteria at time of admission?","answers":[{"option":"AST > 250 IU/L","bool":false},{"option":"LDH > 350 IU/L","bool":false},{"option":"Blood glucose > 200 mg/dL","bool":false},{"option":"Age > 55 years","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium < 8 mg/dL","bool":true}]},{"id":11,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the correct unit for body mass index (BMI)?","answers":[{"option":"kilogram/meter","bool":false},{"option":"kilogram^2/meter^3","bool":false},{"option":"pound/meter^2","bool":false},{"option":"kilogram/meter^2","bool":true},{"option":"no units","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 15-year-old boy presents to the clinic with increased bloating, abdominal pain, and explosive diarrhea upon ingestion of dairy products for the past several months. What is the most likely etiology for this condition?","answers":[{"option":"Villous blunting","bool":false},{"option":"Irritable bowel syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Disaccharidase deficiency","bool":true},{"option":"Tropical sprue","bool":false},{"option":"Giardiasis","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What site of the gastrointestinal tract is involved, as a rule, in ulcerative colitis?","answers":[{"option":"Transverse colon","bool":false},{"option":"Cecum and distal ileum","bool":false},{"option":"Rectum","bool":true},{"option":"Ascending colon","bool":false},{"option":"Anal canal","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common site involved in Crohn's disease?","answers":[{"option":"Ileocecal valve","bool":false},{"option":"Terminal ileum","bool":false},{"option":"Cecum","bool":false},{"option":"Terminal ileum and colon both","bool":true},{"option":"Colon","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is an important complication of severe ulcerative colitis?","answers":[{"option":"Toxic megacolon","bool":true},{"option":"Pyoderma gangrenosum","bool":false},{"option":"Enteropathic arthritis","bool":false},{"option":"Anal fistulae and abscesses","bool":false},{"option":"Cholelithiasis","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common cause of viral gastroenteritis in children?","answers":[{"option":"Rotavirus","bool":true},{"option":"Astrovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Poliovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Norovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Adenovirus","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common site of metastasis of colorectal cancer?","answers":[{"option":"Brain","bool":false},{"option":"Liver","bool":true},{"option":"Lung","bool":false},{"option":"Bones","bool":false},{"option":"Anal canal","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the investigation of choice to determine patency of the distal portion of intestine prior to a defunctioning stoma reversal surgery?","answers":[{"option":"Contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CECT)","bool":false},{"option":"Sigmoidoscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Barium follow-through","bool":false},{"option":"Colonoscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Loopogram","bool":true}]},{"id":19,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which benign tumor is characteristically associated with combined oral contraceptive use?","answers":[{"option":"Hepatic adenoma","bool":true},{"option":"Ovarian cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Colorectal carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Uterine cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Angiosarcoma","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the drug of choice for motion sickness?","answers":[{"option":"Cyclizine","bool":false},{"option":"Promethazine","bool":false},{"option":"Metoclopramide","bool":false},{"option":"Dextroamphetamine","bool":false},{"option":"Hyoscine","bool":true}]},{"id":21,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 30-year-old female is diagnosed with Whipple's disease and discharged following a week of hospital stay and parenteral antibiotic therapy. What antibiotic will be prescribed in this case to be consumed for 12 months?","answers":[{"option":"Benzylpenicillin","bool":false},{"option":"Co-amoxiclav","bool":false},{"option":"Levofloxacin","bool":false},{"option":"Co-trimoxazole","bool":true},{"option":"Rifampicin","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common position employed for examination of a rape victim?","answers":[{"option":"Knee-elbow position","bool":false},{"option":"According to the victim's wishes","bool":false},{"option":"Sim's position","bool":false},{"option":"Lithotomy position","bool":true},{"option":"Knee-chest position","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 65-year-old man suffered a gunshot injury to the head and the surgical team decides to leave the bullet in its place. What is the correct terminology for this?","answers":[{"option":"Retained bullet","bool":false},{"option":"Magic bullet","bool":false},{"option":"Clinical bullet","bool":false},{"option":"Saved bullet","bool":false},{"option":"Souvenir bullet","bool":true}]},{"id":24,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Who is the most commonly affected individual in a road traffic accident?","answers":[{"option":"Driver","bool":false},{"option":"Frontseat passenger","bool":false},{"option":"Backseat passenger","bool":false},{"option":"Sidewalk pedestrian","bool":false},{"option":"Road-crossing pedestrian","bool":true}]},{"id":25,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Hookworm is transmitted in what form?","answers":[{"option":"Eggs","bool":false},{"option":"Larva","bool":true},{"option":"Ova","bool":false},{"option":"Adult","bool":false},{"option":"Larva and ova both","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Salt and pepper appearance on microscopy are seen in which tumor?","answers":[{"option":"Adenocarcinoma diffuse type","bool":false},{"option":"Carcinoid tumor","bool":true},{"option":"Gastrointestinal stomal tumor","bool":false},{"option":"Adenocarcinoma intestinal type","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatocellular carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the Marquis test used for?","answers":[{"option":"Dhatura poisoning","bool":false},{"option":"Opium poisoning","bool":true},{"option":"Cannabis indica poisoning","bool":false},{"option":"Alcohol poisoning","bool":false},{"option":"Benzodiazepine poisoning","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Bile contains which of the following pigments?","answers":[{"option":"Lecithin","bool":false},{"option":"Sphingomyelin","bool":false},{"option":"Biliverdin","bool":false},{"option":"Bilirubin","bool":true},{"option":"Hemosiderin","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"The Rule of Nines is used for which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Electrical injury","bool":false},{"option":"Head trauma","bool":false},{"option":"Burns","bool":true},{"option":"Fractures","bool":false},{"option":"Datura poisoning","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Protein and calorie malnutrition is found in which of the following diseases?","answers":[{"option":"Scurvy","bool":false},{"option":"Rickets","bool":false},{"option":"Marasmus","bool":true},{"option":"Starvation","bool":false},{"option":"Kwashiorkor","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 22-year-old girl develops severe retching with nausea and vomiting. She later has hematemesis of about 200 ml. Which of the following is the most probable cause of hematemesis?","answers":[{"option":"Duodenal ulcer","bool":false},{"option":"Gastritis","bool":false},{"option":"Gastroesophageal reflux disease","bool":false},{"option":"Gastric ulcer","bool":false},{"option":"Mallory Weiss tear","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which is true regarding achalasia?","answers":[{"option":"Increased lower esophageal sphincter tone","bool":true},{"option":"Absence of myenteric plexes","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased lower esophageal sphincter tone","bool":false},{"option":"Absence of Auerbach's plexus","bool":false},{"option":"Increased upper esophageal sphincter tone","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Cyclizine belongs to which class of drugs?","answers":[{"option":"Fifth generation anti-histamine","bool":false},{"option":"First generation anti-histamine","bool":true},{"option":"Second generation anti-histamine","bool":false},{"option":"Fourth generation anti-hitsamine","bool":false},{"option":"Third generation anti-histamine","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common sign of hepatic obstruction?","answers":[{"option":"Edema","bool":false},{"option":"Melena","bool":false},{"option":"Asterixis","bool":false},{"option":"Jaundice","bool":true},{"option":"Hematemesis","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Nitrogen is excreted mainly in which form?","answers":[{"option":"Ammonia","bool":false},{"option":"Urea","bool":true},{"option":"Bile salts","bool":false},{"option":"Uric acid","bool":false},{"option":"Urobilin","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the recommended daily intake of protein for an adult?","answers":[{"option":"100 g/kg","bool":false},{"option":"0.8 g/kg","bool":true},{"option":"1.0 g/kg","bool":false},{"option":"0.1 g/kg","bool":false},{"option":"3 g/kg","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"When aerial oxidation occurs of unsaturated fat what is this referred to?","answers":[{"option":"Oxygenation","bool":false},{"option":"Rancidity","bool":true},{"option":"Reduction","bool":false},{"option":"Pasteurization","bool":false},{"option":"Hydrolysis","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is true regarding aconite?","answers":[{"option":"Has a distinct garlicky odour","bool":false},{"option":"Ideal homicidal poison","bool":true},{"option":"Distinct color when mixed with water","bool":false},{"option":"Expensive to procure","bool":false},{"option":"Leaves a sharp taste in the mouth","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the treatment for grade 3 ascites?","answers":[{"option":"Spironolactone","bool":false},{"option":"Vasopressin","bool":false},{"option":"Furosemide","bool":false},{"option":"Paracentesis","bool":true},{"option":"Albumin","bool":false}]},{"id":40,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the least invasive diagnostic test for gall stones?","answers":[{"option":"Biopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Exploratory laparotomy","bool":false},{"option":"Endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP)","bool":false},{"option":"Endoscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":true}]},{"id":41,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What are Mallory bodies?","answers":[{"option":"Remnants of erythrocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Eosinophilic remnants of hepatocyte apoptosis","bool":false},{"option":"Accumulations of immunoglobulins","bool":false},{"option":"Cytoplasmic inclusions of hepatocytes with keratin","bool":true},{"option":"Calcium and protein inclusions","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A primigravida woman presents to the clinic with yellow discoloration of the sclera for 15 days. Which of the following is likely the cause of hepatitis in pregnant women?","answers":[{"option":"Hepatitis D","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis E","bool":true},{"option":"Hepatitis C","bool":false},{"option":"Autoimmune hepatitis","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis B","bool":false}]},{"id":43,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What disease shows the salt-and-pepper appearance of chromatin upon biopsy?","answers":[{"option":"Hepatocellular carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Adenocarcinoma intestinal type","bool":false},{"option":"Adenocarcinoma diffuse type","bool":false},{"option":"Pancreatic carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Carcinoid tumor","bool":true}]},{"id":44,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is true about pleomorphic adenoma?","answers":[{"option":"Mucous cells are seen only","bool":false},{"option":"Tumor of myoepithelial cells and chondroid tissue","bool":true},{"option":"Has germinal centers","bool":false},{"option":"Squamous cells are predominant","bool":false},{"option":"Has a cystic appearance","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Dysentery is caused by an organism that will also lead to Reiter's syndrome. What is this organism?","answers":[{"option":"Rota virus","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis D","bool":false},{"option":"Shigella","bool":true},{"option":"Helicobacter pylori","bool":false},{"option":"Enterovirus","bool":false}]},{"id":46,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the incubation period for hepatitis A?","answers":[{"option":"30-40 days","bool":false},{"option":"2-7 days","bool":false},{"option":"1-5 days","bool":false},{"option":"10-14 days","bool":false},{"option":"21-30 days","bool":true}]},{"id":47,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common position of the appendix?","answers":[{"option":"Retrocecal","bool":true},{"option":"Rectouterine","bool":false},{"option":"Rectosigmoid","bool":false},{"option":"Rectovesicular","bool":false},{"option":"Transverse","bool":false}]},{"id":48,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Pirenzipine belongs to which class of drugs?","answers":[{"option":"Anti-emetic","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-muscarinic","bool":true},{"option":"Anti-histamine","bool":false},{"option":"Cholinesterase inhibitors","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-inflammatory","bool":false}]},{"id":49,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the best investigation for a liver abscess?","answers":[{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":true},{"option":"Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)","bool":false},{"option":"X-ray","bool":false},{"option":"Biopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Endoscopy","bool":false}]},{"id":50,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the empirical treatment for diarrhea?","answers":[{"option":"Doxycycline","bool":false},{"option":"Ciprofloxacin","bool":true},{"option":"Ampicillin","bool":false},{"option":"Erythromycin","bool":false},{"option":"Metronidazole","bool":false}]},{"id":51,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common site of diverticulosis?","answers":[{"option":"Rectosigmoid junction","bool":false},{"option":"Transverse colon","bool":false},{"option":"Descending colon","bool":false},{"option":"Ascending colon","bool":false},{"option":"Sigmoid colon","bool":true}]},{"id":52,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What type of ulcer is found in abdominal tuberculosis?","answers":[{"option":"Transverse","bool":true},{"option":"Irregular","bool":false},{"option":"Erythmatous","bool":false},{"option":"Well-defined","bool":false},{"option":"Punched-out","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 29-year-old woman presents to the emergency with abdominal distension and intense itchiness all over her body. She complains of fatigue for more than a week and soon after the itchiness began. Her alkaline phosphatase (ALP) is 300 U/L and aspartate transaminase (AST) is 95 U/L. What is the diagnostic investigation for her symptoms?","answers":[{"option":"Antinuclear antibodies","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":false},{"option":"Serum albumin","bool":false},{"option":"Antimitochondrial antibodies","bool":true},{"option":"Pancreatic enzymes","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 38-year-old man presents to the clinic with yellow discoloration of the sclera and skin. He had a transfusion 8 years ago and has had multiple transfusions for various reasons over the past few years. What is the most likely cause of his symptoms?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis A","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis D","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis E","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatitis C","bool":true}]},{"id":55,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 20-year-old man presents to the outpatient clinic with speech impairment, muscle stiffness, and gait abnormalities. An ophthalmic examination revealed a cherry-red spot on the macula. Abdominal examination findings included hepatosplenomegaly. What is the next investiagtion?","answers":[{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":false},{"option":"Liver biopsy","bool":true},{"option":"X-ray","bool":false},{"option":"Abdominal CT scan","bool":false},{"option":"Endoscopy","bool":false}]},{"id":56,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Encephalopathy, wrist-drop, and constipation are the triad most commonly seen in which of the following toxicities?","answers":[{"option":"Thallium","bool":false},{"option":"Arsenic","bool":false},{"option":"Phosphorous","bool":false},{"option":"Mercury","bool":false},{"option":"Lead","bool":true}]},{"id":57,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 30-year-old unmarried woman comes into the outpatient department with a complaint of constipation. What is the doctor most likely to recommend for her condition?","answers":[{"option":"Tell her to eat more dairy products","bool":false},{"option":"Avoid gluten","bool":false},{"option":"Prescribe anti-emetics","bool":false},{"option":"Increase protein intake","bool":false},{"option":"Increase dietary roughage intake","bool":true}]},{"id":58,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What aggravates the symptoms of an insulinoma?","answers":[{"option":"Dehydration","bool":false},{"option":"Glucose","bool":false},{"option":"Exercise","bool":true},{"option":"High-carbohydrate diet","bool":false},{"option":"High-protein diet","bool":false}]},{"id":59,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A convex-shaped hyperdense figure is seen on a head computed tomography (CT) scan. What is the diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Subarachnoid hematoma","bool":false},{"option":"Epidural hematoma","bool":true},{"option":"Infarct","bool":false},{"option":"Subdural hematoma","bool":false},{"option":"Meningitis","bool":false}]},{"id":60,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common site of a squamous cell carcinoma of the esophagus?","answers":[{"option":"Base of the tongue","bool":false},{"option":"Lower 2/3","bool":false},{"option":"Middle 1/3","bool":true},{"option":"Upper 2/3","bool":false},{"option":"Halfway to the stomach","bool":false}]},{"id":61,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following best describes kleptomania?","answers":[{"option":"Low moods for 3 weeks","bool":false},{"option":"Elevated mood and intense elation without cause","bool":false},{"option":"Belief that everyone is spying on you","bool":false},{"option":"Irresistible urge to steal things","bool":true},{"option":"Firmly believing the world is meaningless and does not exist","bool":false}]},{"id":62,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following polyps has the most malignant potential?","answers":[{"option":"Hamartomatous","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudopolyps","bool":false},{"option":"Tubular","bool":false},{"option":"Hyperplastic","bool":false},{"option":"Villous","bool":true}]},{"id":63,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the histopathological form of squamous cell carcinoma of the esophagus?","answers":[{"option":"Keratinized","bool":true},{"option":"Pedunculated","bool":false},{"option":"Exophytic","bool":false},{"option":"Flat","bool":false},{"option":"Diffuse","bool":false}]},{"id":64,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the treatment for a tumor on the liver that is 2 cm?","answers":[{"option":"Radiotherapy","bool":false},{"option":"Embolization","bool":false},{"option":"Resection","bool":true},{"option":"Chemotherapy","bool":false},{"option":"Transplant","bool":false}]},{"id":65,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is seen on the body when a high-velocity bullet strikes?","answers":[{"option":"Blackening","bool":false},{"option":"Wound of entry and exit both present","bool":true},{"option":"Crocodile skin","bool":false},{"option":"Singeing","bool":false},{"option":"Permanent cavity formed","bool":false}]},{"id":66,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Arborescent marks on the skin are seen in which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Primary impact of explosions","bool":false},{"option":"Burns from a housefire","bool":false},{"option":"Radiation burns","bool":false},{"option":"Sulphuric acid","bool":false},{"option":"Lightening","bool":true}]},{"id":67,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"How is the immunity towards hepatitis B virus measured?","answers":[{"option":"HBsAg","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-HBeAb","bool":false},{"option":"HBcAg","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-HBcAb","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-HBsAb","bool":true}]},{"id":68,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following organisms is associated with Reiter's syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Streptococcus pyogenes","bool":false},{"option":"Bacillus anthracosis","bool":false},{"option":"Staphylococcal aureus","bool":false},{"option":"Helicobacter pylori","bool":false},{"option":"Campylobacter jejuni","bool":true}]},{"id":69,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A painless enlarged gallbladder is associated with which of the following diseases?","answers":[{"option":"Pancreatic carcinoma","bool":true},{"option":"Cholelithiasis","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatoma","bool":false},{"option":"Acute pancreatitis","bool":false},{"option":"Acute cholecystitis","bool":false}]},{"id":70,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the most common site of peptic ulcer disease?","answers":[{"option":"Esophagus","bool":false},{"option":"Lower esophageal sphincter","bool":false},{"option":"Pyloric sphincter","bool":false},{"option":"Duodenum","bool":true},{"option":"Antrum of the stomach","bool":false}]},{"id":71,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"In the adenoma-carcinoma sequence for colorectal carcinomas, what is the second hit in the 'two-hit hypothesis'?","answers":[{"option":"Inheritance of mutated allele","bool":false},{"option":"Overexpression in COX-2","bool":false},{"option":"Methylation of normal APC allele","bool":true},{"option":"Mutation in proto-oncogenes","bool":false},{"option":"Deletions in DCC gene","bool":false}]},{"id":72,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"In colorectal cancer which of the following is the first event to occur?","answers":[{"option":"Loss of tumor suppressor genes","bool":false},{"option":"Proliferation of polyps","bool":false},{"option":"Unregulated intracellular signaling","bool":false},{"option":"Inheritance of mutated APC allele","bool":true},{"option":"Mutation in proto-oncogenes","bool":false}]},{"id":73,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A patient has repeated episodes of emesis and epigastric pain upon eating meals and before sleeping. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Celiac disease","bool":false},{"option":"Duodenal ulcer","bool":false},{"option":"Gastric ulcer","bool":true},{"option":"GERD","bool":false},{"option":"Cholelithiasis","bool":false}]},{"id":74,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"A 38-year-old man presents to the clinic with a 6-month history of heartburn. He is sent for endoscopy which revealed pinkish mucosa on the esophagus near the gastro-esophageal junction. What is the diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Crohn's disease","bool":false},{"option":"Achalasia","bool":false},{"option":"Barret esophagus","bool":true},{"option":"Boerhaave syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"GERD","bool":false}]},{"id":75,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"In which of the following conditions is misoprostol given?","answers":[{"option":"Pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"NSAID induced ulcers","bool":true},{"option":"Adenocarcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Juvenile polyposis","bool":false},{"option":"Zollinger-Ellison syndrome","bool":false}]},{"id":76,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the dietary advice given to a patient with cirrhosis?","answers":[{"option":"Decreased saturated fat intake","bool":true},{"option":"Decrease protein intake","bool":false},{"option":"Increase sugar intake","bool":false},{"option":"Decrease complex carbohydrate intake","bool":false},{"option":"Decrease fiber intake","bool":false}]},{"id":77,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which morphological change is observed in the villi in celiac disease?","answers":[{"option":"Metaplasia","bool":false},{"option":"Dysplasia","bool":false},{"option":"Atrophy","bool":true},{"option":"Hyperplasia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypertrophy","bool":false}]},{"id":78,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following sentences describes celiac disease morphology?","answers":[{"option":"Creeping fat with transmural inflammation","bool":false},{"option":"Crypt hyperplasia, intraepithelial lymphocytosis, and villous atrophy","bool":true},{"option":"Dysplasia of intraepithelial cells","bool":false},{"option":"Crypt abscesses with neutrophil infiltrates","bool":false},{"option":"Cobble-stoning of the mucosal lining","bool":false}]},{"id":79,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following groups of cells is responsible for causing celiac disease?","answers":[{"option":"CD4+ T-cells","bool":true},{"option":"CD8+ T-cells","bool":false},{"option":"Plasma cells","bool":false},{"option":"B-cells","bool":false},{"option":"Cytotoxic killer T-cells","bool":false}]},{"id":80,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is the feature of small bowel dilation on X-ray?","answers":[{"option":"Haustrations","bool":false},{"option":"Coffee-bean sign","bool":false},{"option":"Valvulae conniventes","bool":true},{"option":"Step-ladder appearance","bool":false},{"option":"Apple-core sign","bool":false}]},{"id":81,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is a common cause of pseudoobstruction?","answers":[{"option":"Low fiber diet","bool":false},{"option":"Anorexia","bool":false},{"option":"Surgery","bool":true},{"option":"Polyps","bool":false},{"option":"Carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":82,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is true regarding gastric carcinoma?","answers":[{"option":"Diffuse type has ulcers","bool":false},{"option":"Gastric adenocarcinomas are chemosensitive","bool":false},{"option":"Intestinal type is associated with H. pylori","bool":true},{"option":"Diffuse type has a good prognosis","bool":false},{"option":"Gastric adenocarcinomas have good prognosis","bool":false}]},{"id":83,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following secretes bicarbonate ions?","answers":[{"option":"Esophageal glands","bool":false},{"option":"Pancreas","bool":true},{"option":"Duodenum","bool":false},{"option":"Liver","bool":false},{"option":"Stomach antrum","bool":false}]},{"id":84,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"When is pepsinogen activated?","answers":[{"option":"Increased OH- concentrations","bool":false},{"option":"Increased H+ concentrations","bool":true},{"option":"Neutral solutions","bool":false},{"option":"Increased HCO3- concentrations","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased H+ concentrations","bool":false}]},{"id":85,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is stimulated by secretin to release bicarbonate ions?","answers":[{"option":"Biliary tree","bool":false},{"option":"Pancreas","bool":true},{"option":"Chief cells","bool":false},{"option":"Parietal cells","bool":false},{"option":"Crypts of Lieberkuhn","bool":false}]},{"id":86,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What metabolic disorder is seen in gastric outlet obstruction?","answers":[{"option":"Hyperchloremic metabolic acidosis","bool":false},{"option":"Hypochloremic metabolic acidosis","bool":false},{"option":"Hypochloremic metabolic alkalosis","bool":true},{"option":"Hyperchloremic metabolic alkalosis","bool":false},{"option":"Normal anion gap metabolic alkalosis","bool":false}]},{"id":87,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is incorrect about proton pump inhibitors?","answers":[{"option":"Decrease absorption of Ca and Mg","bool":false},{"option":"They inhibit H/K/ATPase","bool":false},{"option":"Concomitant use with H2 inhibitors is recommended","bool":true},{"option":"Can lead to pneumonia","bool":false},{"option":"Increase risk for C. difficile infection","bool":false}]},{"id":88,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which statement is incorrect about H2 inhibitors?","answers":[{"option":"Cimetidine causes increased prolactin","bool":false},{"option":"Inhibit gastrin secretion","bool":true},{"option":"Act on parietal cells","bool":false},{"option":"Reversibly block H2 receptors","bool":false},{"option":"Inhibit acid secretion","bool":false}]},{"id":89,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following fractures is a warning sign of child abuse?","answers":[{"option":"Galeazzi","bool":false},{"option":"Spiral","bool":true},{"option":"Greenstick","bool":false},{"option":"Transverse","bool":false},{"option":"Comminuted","bool":false}]},{"id":90,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Schizophrenia is defined as which type of disorder?","answers":[{"option":"Neurotic","bool":false},{"option":"Psychotic","bool":true},{"option":"Somatiform","bool":false},{"option":"Mood","bool":false},{"option":"Anxiety","bool":false}]},{"id":91,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is a hallucination?","answers":[{"option":"True perceptions in the presence of external stimuli","bool":false},{"option":"Inappropriate perception in the presence of external stimuli","bool":false},{"option":"False perception in the absence of external stimuli","bool":true},{"option":"Firm belief that has social backing","bool":false},{"option":"False firm belief conflicting with reality","bool":false}]},{"id":92,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Marquis test is used in which toxicity?","answers":[{"option":"Organophosphates","bool":false},{"option":"Opioid","bool":true},{"option":"Benzodiazepines","bool":false},{"option":"Acetaminophen","bool":false},{"option":"Aspirin","bool":false}]},{"id":93,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Which of the following is true regarding alcohol?","answers":[{"option":"Absolute spirit has 110% ethanol","bool":false},{"option":"Rectified spirit is 75% ethanol","bool":false},{"option":"Offences occur at 300ml of intoxication","bool":false},{"option":"Vitamin C is a useful antidote in alcohol poisoning","bool":false},{"option":"Delirium is a sign of intoxication","bool":true}]},{"id":94,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"Old proteins are replaced by new ones repeatedly. What is this called?","answers":[{"option":"Protein count","bool":false},{"option":"Protein metabolism","bool":false},{"option":"Protein output","bool":false},{"option":"Protein turnover","bool":true},{"option":"Protein calorie count","bool":false}]},{"id":95,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the first step in the management of strychnine poisoning?","answers":[{"option":"Tracheostomy","bool":false},{"option":"Remove all clothes","bool":false},{"option":"IV benzodiazepines","bool":true},{"option":"Place patient in a dark room","bool":false},{"option":"Stomach wash","bool":false}]},{"id":96,"info":"3rd-year/gastrointestinal/2017","question":"What is the mechanism of action of castor oil?","answers":[{"option":"Burns skin and other linings","bool":false},{"option":"Irritates skin","bool":false},{"option":"Inhibits neurones in anterior horn","bool":false},{"option":"Corrodes mucous membranes","bool":false},{"option":"Stimulates motility","bool":true}]}]
export default arr